Guide to the Arthur Peterson papers,1920-1976
Peterson, Arthur papers, 1920-1976
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Arthur Peterson papers, 1920-1976
7-1-1808
Arthur Peterson
16 cubic feet.
{comma separted list of material formats; end with period.}
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Subject files, department records, and financial records of the Office of the Treasurer.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Treasurer, Cornell University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Subject files, department records, and financial records of the Office of the Treasurer.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Peterson, Arthur; Cornell University--Administration
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Life Safety and Insurance (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Marsh & McLennon (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Program - Cornell University Centennial Celebration (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Road Proposal - Bypass Road to Rt. 13 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Building and Grounds Contract #9604 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Public Works Contracts (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Proposed Entomology Complex - College of Agriculture - Cornell University (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Central Construction Requests (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Report on State Lands Records - State Appropriations to the College of Agriculture - New York Consolidated Laws (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Centennial Planning Committee Meeting, June 4, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Dean's Meeting Minutes (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Dean, Arthur (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Defense Contract Audit Agency - Audit Reports (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Overhead Calculation - Revised Budget - Cornell SUCF Meeting (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Defense Contract Audit (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Deep Purple (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Deferred Compensation (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Desch, Noel (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Design & Project Management (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Development Office (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Discipline & Judicial System at Cornell University (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Dining Services (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Drum Corps International (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Durland, L. H. (Permanent File) (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Early Retirement (Box 1, Folder 25)
- EEO-6 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Egner, Anton & Associates (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Employee Compensation & Fringe Benefits Administration (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Educational Development (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Endowed Professorships (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Endowment Funds (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Engineering College (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Entomology & Limnology (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Fair Labor Standard Act (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Fiscal Responsibility Center (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Food Science Department (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Ford Foundation (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Freeville Field Laboratory (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Fringe Benefits Administration (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Overhead Rates (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Telephones (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Council on Economic & Cultural Affairs - Farm Mgt. Grant - von Oppenfield & Bond (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Fire Safety Measures - Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Reports (Box 2, Folder 5)
- By Laws (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Tuition (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous Legislation & Rulings (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Mr. Richard Braun (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Ford Foundation Extension Adm. (Box 2, Folder 10)
- State University Tuition (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Fire Safety Survey for Cornell University (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Fire Safety Survey for Cornell University (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Married Student Housing for Cornell University (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Finance and Business Office (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Gaslight Village (Box 2, Folder 16)
- General Services Budget (Box 2, Folder 17)
- General Services - Wally Rogers (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Golden Nematode Research Farm - Plattsburg, N.Y. (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Golden Nematode Laboratory - Farmingdale, New York (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Graduate School (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Grumman Squash Courts (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Gurowitz, William - Vice President for Campus affairs (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Hansen, inc. A.S.-J. Russell Southworth (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Haskins & Sells (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Health Services (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Heating Plant Alterations (Permanent File) (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Herbster, William (Box 2, Folder 28)
- HEW - Health, Education & Welfare (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Housing Department (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Human Ecology (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Information Associates, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 32)
- IBM - 370/168 Computer (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Industrial & Labor Relations (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Internal Revenue (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Isle of Shoals (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Jackson, P. P. (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Long Island Vegetable Research Farm (Box 3, Folder 1)
- McGuire & Bennett, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 2)
- McKeegan, Paul, Vice Provost (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Major Employers Group (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Medical College (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Medical College Auditorium Agreement (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Medical College - Agreement File (Permanent) (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Medical College "S" Building Agreement (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Meyer, Elmer, Jr. Dean of Students (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Minority Education at Cornell (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Monarch Entertainment Bureau (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Morgan Guaranty Trust Company (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Morrill Hall (Box 3, Folder 14)
- MSA (Box 3, Folder 15)
- North Campus Renovations (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Nutrition, School of (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Cornell State University (Box 3, Folder 18)
- New York State Cooperative Extension Service - Classification and Compensation Plan for Professional Personnel (Box 3, Folder 19)
- A Summary: Cooperative Extension Service Matters for Policy Consideration by Cornell University Officials (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Hotel - State vs. Endowed Status (Box 3, Folder 21)
- New York State Cooperative Extension Service - Classification and Compensation Plan for Professional Personnel (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Misc. Financial Reports & Studies (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Faculty Salary Studies, 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Endowed Faculty Salaries, 1957-1958 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Faculty Salaries, 1960-1961 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Faculty Salaries, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Faculty Salaries, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Faculty Salaries, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Faculty Salaries, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Campus Store Management Contract (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Faculty Salaries, 1972-1975 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Registration (Box 3, Folder 33)
- State University - Master Plan - Commitments - Numbers (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Facilities Projected for Contruction or Acquisition by or Sooner - State University of New York, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Outline Study - Feasibility of Proposed Connecting Additions - Stone Hall, Roberts Hall, East Roberts Hall (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Financial Extension Projects, 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Financial Extension Projects, 1960-1961 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Economic Status Committee Faculty, Tolles Report (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Litigation (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Extension Committee (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Payroll Misc. Information (Box 3, Folder 42)
- N.Y. Foundation Seed Stocks Cooperative (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Buildings and Grounds Maintenance Survey (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Comber Stewart (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Computer Security (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Communication Arts (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Concerts East, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Conference Coordinator - Chris Molt (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Consolidated Budget - Stationary Colleges (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Controller Candidates (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Consolidation of Buildings & Properties Shops (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Contracts (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Cooke, W. A. - Vice Provost (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Cooperative Extension (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Cornellian (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Cornell Charter (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Cornell Children's Tuition (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Cornell Plantations (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Cornell Club (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Cornell Research Foundation (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Cornell University Disability Plan (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Cornell University Press (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Cornell Women's Causcus (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Corson, Dale, President (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Counsel's Offiice (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Cranch Committee (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Credit Union (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Geneva Experiment Station (Box 4, Folder 25)
- State University General (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Parrott Hall (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Department of Agriculture and Markets (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Spindler, Harry (Box 4, Folder 29)
- State Division of Budget (Box 4, Folder 30)
- State Freeze and Budget Cuts (Box 4, Folder 31)
- State University Construction Fund (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Boyer, Ernest L., Chancellor (Box 4, Folder 33)
- State Education Department (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Department of Taxation and Finance (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Agreement Between State of New York & Senate Professional Assoc. (Box 4, Folder 36)
- State Repairs, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Leo Collins - Auditor (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Cornell/SUNY Task Force (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Office of Computer Services (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Executive Staff (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Accessory Instructions (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Agenda Items (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Abbott Associates (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Accounting Department (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Accounts -- Authorized -- Signiture Arthur H. Peterson (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Academic Funding Tom Rogers (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Action Communication Systems, Inc. Watsbox (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Adams committee (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Admissions (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Agriculture & Life Sciences (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Allee Committee Report (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Annual Reports, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Annual Reports, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Agronomy (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Arts & Sciences (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Arecibo (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Aquaculture (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Astronomy (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Alternatives to Selling Stock (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Audit Committee (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Athletic Department (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Animal Science Harford Farm Complex Agreement (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Animal Science Department (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Department of Audit and Control - Audit Reports, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Bailey Hall (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Bad Debts (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Banks (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Bates, Joe (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Barlow, Mark (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Boy Scouts (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Branch Bank (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Barlow, Robert (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Biological Sciences (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Brenner Case (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Budget Office, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Budgets, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- 5 Year Budget (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Budget Task Force Committee (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Bundy Bill (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Bursar's Office - Jim Lyon (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Budget Projections (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Business and Public Administration (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Cade, Tom (Peregrine Falcon Research) (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Campus Life (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Capital Fund (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Car Allowance (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Cashier's Daily Report (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Circular Letters (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Citizen's Bank (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Civil Service Law (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Cline, Marline - Permanent File (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Code of Academic Integrity (Box 5, Folder 53)
- College Fleet (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Collective Bargaining (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Group Life Insurance (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Real Estate Department (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Ratner Report (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Agreements (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Air Travel Insurance (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Errors and Omissions Liability Coverage (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Insurance Coverages (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Student Health Insurance (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Insurance - General (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Workmen's Compensation Account (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Marsh & McLennan Insurance Co. (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Johnson & Higgins (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Pomfrey Company (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Boyce Thompson Agreement No. C 78108 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Boyce Thompson Institute Financing (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Biological Laboratory/Greenhouse Facility (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Biological Laboratory Greenhouse Facility #16029 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Shops Inventory (Box 6, Folder 18)
- University Computing Board (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Listening Post (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Knapp, David, Provost (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Phillips Hall - Clean Room Project (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Union Contract (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Ulrich Franzen & Associates (Box 6, Folder 24)
- State Repairs, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Radiation biology Field Laboratory (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Poultry Science Department (Box 6, Folder 27)
- The Pressprich Corporation (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Pomology Department (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Plant Pathology (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Physical Plant Operations (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Kennedy, Keith, Dean (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Warren Farm (Box 6, Folder 33)
- University Investments - Bob Horn (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Veterinary College (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Long Range Appropriation Figures (Box 7, Folder 1)
- A. I. C. Conference (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Arnot Forest (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Accessory Instruction Report Prepared for State University (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Apprenticeship Standards for the Building Trades in the State College at Cornell University, Ithaca, NY (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Associated Hospital Service of New York (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Budgets, 1951-1952 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- R. S. Breed (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Civil Service (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Civil Service (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Clippings (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Dairy Herd - Geneva (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Dean's Income Fund - Estimates of Expenditures (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Disabled & Non-disabled Veterans Appts. & Promotions after, Jan 1. 1951 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Farm & Home Week Budgets (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Foertsch Restudy of Job Classifications (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Fellowship Award - Council on Economic and Cultural Affairs (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Food Service Committee - John Burton, Chairman (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Harding Case (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Health & Medical Services Committee (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Home Economics Research Projects (Box 7, Folder 21)
- House Rentals (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Special Projects and Contracts (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Ithaca Mild Distribution (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Inter-College Committee (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Z. J. Kertesz F.A.O. Contract (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Mann Hall Equipment (Box 7, Folder 27)
- James J. McDonnell Foreign Student (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Motor Vehical Equipment (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Reports on Persons Entering Military Services (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Military Regulations (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Office Foreign Agricultural Relations (Box 7, Folder 32)
- N.Y.S. Electric & Gas Corp. & Geneva Experiment Station (Box 7, Folder 33)
- President's Cabinet (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Publications Committee (Box 7, Folder 35)
- R.M.A. (Box 7, Folder 36)
- School of I. & L. R. State Dept. Contract - German Students (Box 7, Folder 37)
- O. R. O. German Project Edwin F. Beal I. & L. R. (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Repair Reports, 1954-1955 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Repair Reports, 1954-1955 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Repair Work (Box 7, Folder 41)
- J. H. Roberts File (Box 7, Folder 42)
- State Retirement System - Applications for Service Retirement (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Safety Supervisor (Box 7, Folder 44)
- School of Nutrition (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Scientific Meetings Dept. Schedule (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Mr. Aslam Siddiqu (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Space Requests (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Staff (Terms of Appointment) (Box 7, Folder 49)
- State Audit and Control Forms - Rewrite Checks (Box 7, Folder 50)
- Summer School, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 51)
- Summer School, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 52)
- Television Proposal (Box 7, Folder 53)
- The MacMillan Co. Bailey Hortorium Royalty Account (Box 7, Folder 54)
- College of Agriculture Places for 1920 (Box 7, Folder 55)
- Wheat Acreage (Box 7, Folder 56)
- American Council on Education Special Committee (Box 7, Folder 57)
- United States of America Operations Mission to the Philippines (Box 7, Folder 58)
- Cornell University State-Supported Unites Report on Reconnaissance Review of Business Office Organization and Procedures (Box 7, Folder 59)
- Organization Chart of New York State College of Agriculture (Box 7, Folder 60)
- Special Committee on Campus Traffic Problems Reports (Box 7, Folder 61)
- Ithaca - Residential Parking (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Board on Traffic Control (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Board on Traffic Control 1955 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Traffic Study Tabulations (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Traffic Meeting (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Board on Traffic Control (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Twenty-five Year Recognition Ceremony (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Better Traffic Administration for Ithaca (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Cornell Campus Store, Inc., 1956 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory, Inc., 1956 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Cornell University, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Agricultural EngineeringProgress Reports on Research (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Personnel Manual Cornell University (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Research in the Agronomy Department, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Cornell Campus Store, Inc., 1957 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory, Inc., 1957 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Cornell University, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Traffic Survey Questionnaire Returns, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Agricultural Dean & Directors Meetings (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Medical Expense Insurance State-Endowed (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Administrative Staff Meetings, 1955-1956; 1958 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Administrative Staff Meetings, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Rotary Club (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Repair File, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Repair File, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Repair Reserve, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Repair Reserve, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- General Services State Repair Reserve, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- IBM Data Processing - Cornell University (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Construction & Repairs - Weekly Job Reports (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Miscellaneous, 1956-1958 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Administrative Staff Meetings, 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Administrative Staff Meetings, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Construction and Repairs, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Preliminary Information - Animal Disease Laboratory (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Facts Presented - Animal Disease Laboratory (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Expansion of Cornell Library (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Staff Loads (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Report of the Dean of the N.Y.S. School of I. & L. R., 1953-1954 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Bailey Hall Seats (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Charles S. Brown Estate (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Traffic Committee (Box 8, Folder 42)
- State College Programs (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Return for Tax Exemption: Farm & Home Bureau & 4-H Club Assoc. (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Sun Oil Co. Nitrogen Fertilizer Grant (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Kellogg Evaluation Studies (Box 8, Folder 46)
- Barton Hall Survey (Box 8, Folder 47)
- Golf Course (Box 8, Folder 48)
- Lloyd Library & Museum Wild Life Preserve (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Sale of Products Policy (Box 9, Folder 2)
- University Policies (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Geneva Experiment Station (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Conservation Department (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Drill Hall (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Extension Department (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Hans Guenther Brandes - State Dept. Contract (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Occupational Retirement Committee (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Dr. Bradford - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Council Meetings, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Cornell Related Activities (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Champion Case (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Cresap, McCormick & Paget (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Country Club Property (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Farm Electrification Council (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Alfred C. Hottes Estate (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Hotel School (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Undergraduate Research Participation Program - National Science Foundation (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Auto Crash Injury (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Automotive Crash Injury Research Exhibits (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Management Record, Sept. 1956 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Comparative Analysis Blue Cross Blue Shield vs. Insured Plan (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Analysis of Massachusetts Mutual life Insurance Company as the Carrier for the Employee Benefit Plan (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Proposed Plan of Group Insurance (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Blue Cross & Blue Shield Hospital & Medical Plans (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Excess Medical Reimbursement Insurance (Box 9, Folder 27)
- N. Y. Life Insurance - Excess Medical Policy (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Excess Medical Insurance - Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Positions Transferred (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Extension Committee (Box 9, Folder 31)
- School of Nutrition (Box 9, Folder 32)
- F. F. Hill - Consultant Service (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Horner Report - Syracuse Forestry (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Extension - Legislation. Constitution Bylaws (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Edwin Moore (Box 9, Folder 36)
- National Science Foundation (Box 9, Folder 37)
- State Automative Contracts (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Supervisor Committee (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Geneva Labor Situation (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Grievance-Technical Employees, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Medical College (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Membership and Dues Payment (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Middle States Evaluation Inquiry (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Building Remodeling (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Natural Areas Comm. (Box 9, Folder 46)
- New Endowments (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Nuclear Studies (Box 9, Folder 48)
- School of Nutrition (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Olin, Spencer - Civil Eng. Bldg. Gift (Box 9, Folder 50)
- Allen-Kellogg Dispute (Box 9, Folder 51)
- Director of the Laboratory of Ornithology (Box 9, Folder 52)
- Laboratory of Ornithology (Box 9, Folder 53)
- Patent Policy (Box 9, Folder 54)
- Payroll Committee (Box 9, Folder 55)
- Performing Arts. Comm. (Box 9, Folder 56)
- A. H. Peterson - Personal (Box 9, Folder 57)
- Pesticide Residue Analytical Laboratory (Box 9, Folder 58)
- Plant Breeding Dept. (Box 9, Folder 59)
- Plant Pathology Dept. (Box 9, Folder 60)
- Pomology Dept. (Box 9, Folder 61)
- Poultry Dept. (Box 9, Folder 62)
- Post Office (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Provost Corson (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Purchasing Dept. (Box 10, Folder 3)
- School of I. & L. R., 1960-1964 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- School of I. & L. R., 1960-1962 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Reading & Study Skills Center (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Regional History & University Archives (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Houses rented by College of Agric. (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Requisitions (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Rockefeller-Plant Physiol. Grants (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Rural Education and Sociology Depts. (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Rynalski Farm (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Sabbatical Leaves (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Salaries (Box 10, Folder 14)
- School of Education (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Scholar Incentive Award (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Savings Bank (Box 10, Folder 17)
- 4-G Club - School Drop-out Program (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Salvage (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Sewage-Disposal Comm. (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Shackleton Point Rd. (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Shell Fellowships (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Special Payroll Comm. (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Space Requirements (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Simon & Snyder Estates (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Social Security (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Soil Conservation Service (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Special Projects Comm. (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Inter College Comm. (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Statler Inn (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Statler Inn (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Summer Session (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Surplus Property (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Tax Shelter Annuities (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Telephone Division (Box 10, Folder 35)
- National Science Foundation (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Testing Service (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Teachers Insurance & Annuities Association (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Time Records (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Traffic Survey (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Traveling Fellowships (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Travel Requests (Box 10, Folder 42)
- J. B. Trousdale - Personal (Box 10, Folder 43)
- Trudeau Foundation, Inc. (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Tuition and Fees (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Turkey Contract (Box 10, Folder 46)
- College of Agric. & the next quarter century (Box 10, Folder 47)